And we are live. Welcome back on the
Ship Ship Show for a new week. And what
a week. What a week.
>> A busy week.
>> Yes. That That was a fun one. Like
>> it's kind of I I'm fully maxed out on
everything. So
>> yeah. Yeah. I didn't use my codeex reset
yet, but uh I
>> I'm done with CL to account like
bye-bye.
>> Exactly.
>> Yeah. Uh G No. Yeah.
GM O. Oh, forgot the tweet again, but
that's fine. We were making like a so
should be fine. And YouTube, are we live
on YouTube? I think it's going to be
good. Yes, we are live. Let's go. Let's
go. Let's go. Okay, cool. Uh okay. I'm
excited, man. I'm excited. I'm hyped.
>> So, you've just finished your entire
work for the whole year in a week.
>> I'm I'm catching up with what I was late
on the last few months, but uh yeah,
that was that was a week. Okay, I'm
going to do the intro and then we jump
right away and then Okay.
>> Uh okay.
>> Fiber is gone and you are missing it.
And we know that because we are missing
it too and it was already like just
today.
>> Yeah, [laughter]
>> we build a road map in a week that we
were dreaming of for months uh because
fable was so great but now it's gone. So
what are the alternatives? We are going
to dig into that in this video. So uh uh
subscribe, watch the video and like and
share it with your friends.
Nice.
>> Perfect.
>> Oh, okay. Cool. Uh, okay. So, what did
you do with SE 5?
>> Uh, everything.
>> Yeah,
>> I just had Adam check every project
and it created a lot of documentation
and then I was at 2%. So, I thought,
well, let's go.
>> Yes.
>> Because I don't know, but last time it
was was the usage going on much faster.
Right.
>> I Okay, so for me, I slow down on ultra
code.
I put it on high.
>> I I was fable high the whole week.
>> Yes.
>> But only on planning and documentation
and uh stuff like that. And I was I used
ultra code only for when I asked it to
discover something in the codebase.
>> Mhm.
>> But as soon as I had one or two session,
I was taking like 10% of the usage like
nuts. But like it it was like spawning
like Yeah. 100 sub agent worked for 30
minutes. So maybe that's why. But like
the output was nice.
>> Yeah. And I think your code base is much
bigger than the ones that I use.
>> Uh 1 million of code like
>> Yeah, it's bigger. I use it for small
projects as well and that's that's
awesome.
>> Okay. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, there is also
that
um interesting. So just getting a a
something stupid like a WordPress theme
>> that was custommade but like two three
years ago.
>> Yeah.
>> I only downloaded team asked uh Fable to
just update everything
>> and it gave me a list and then it said
please wait and it gave me another list
and it did everything and even Google
page speed went up from like 30 to 98.
>> Damn. It just improved everything.
>> Yeah. I mean like in the data set I can
expect that a lot of WordPress theme and
website and stuff are like it's
basically the front door of internet. So
all of that [__] was been has been
scrapped and all of the public template.
Yeah.
Yeah. That would be Yeah, that's nice.
Um but do you see no like not a value
but like do you see this industry like
dying because now it will be like you
can v one prompt one shot a WordPress
template.
>> No I think the industry is is even going
to get bigger because so many people get
access
>> and they will just create and then if
they want something fixed they still ask
a defaf because they can do everything.
>> Yeah. I mean maybe for the like the big
the big ecom websites.
>> Yeah. But also for small I have a
customer who is creating the entire
design with with claw design.
>> Okay.
>> And he doesn't know how to use FTP. So
he keeps asking me to upload the HTML
files.
>> Why doesn't use He's almost here. He's
almost here.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But this explains people see
how it works. they can do it
>> and they have the design ready and then
they don't know what to do.
>> Yeah. Ah yeah. So they don't have the
knowledge and they don't they didn't ask
okay. So now what do I do to uh to make
it live basically?
>> But then they they need to enter enter a
FTP address or an IP and they don't know
where the IP is so they search their own
IP and they try to link in to the local
network. You know all those funny MS
that people show.
>> Yeah. Um, who is Jason? Well,
>> yeah,
>> actually people are doing it and then
they say I'm out of uh uh of of Google
>> of my site is not indexed and then
you're checking you don't have a sitemap
or they just uploaded all the HTML files
over the WordPress website. So the
WordPress website is still giving the
sitemap and the HTML files are
overriding the PHP file. So you're
seeing a different website and so
honestly
I've seen this at multiple customers who
think that they did it correct and they
are afraid of breaking stuff and don't
know what they're doing. There was still
a lot of work for people who have a
little bit of knowledge.
>> Okay, that's interesting. That's
interesting. Yeah. So there's still a
gap even like if I mean it's like yeah
everyone can
use Photoshop but if you are not not an
artist or like a professional editor you
can prompt what the [__] you want but if
you didn't study light or you have an
understanding of light aspect color
palette color blah blah blah uh then
you're not going to go anywhere.
>> Yeah. And if there is nothing exciting
in your in your hosting,
>> you can just give cloud code, the SSH
key, just give him the username,
password, tell them the IP, it will log
in and it will do everything for you. It
will clean up, it make improvements, it
will do testing,
it does everything.
>> Yeah. Oh yeah, like that that was one of
my big aha moment with AI when uh I set
up a server for genfit
>> and CL did the whole configuration
and three years, five years ago, it
would have take me like maybe
three day to a week to maybe even more
because then you you set up the
configuration but then you forgot a
comma in the nix config file and then
the redirection is not talking and it
took you like three weeks to [__]
find this comma.
>> Yeah. But also, if you want to connect
two servers in the same uh space,
>> you want to do it via private tunnel.
So, you have to set it up. You have to
test everything.
>> And that took so much time. And now you
just say, "Hey, set it up like this,
this, this." And then you do your test,
you give him the results, it finishes,
and it's done.
>> No, not that. But still like we know
what we want, how we want to do it and
which question to ask. So yeah, but
still with that perspective with Fable 5
like what are your first impression of
like using
>> like Yeah. How do how is that different
from Opus 4.8?
Opus just felt like I had still had not
a junior but maybe a meteor and I still
had to give a lot of improvements and
say well you rebuilt everything but I
only wanted to change uh this line in
CSS
>> that would have fixed it. Um and it
would give me options on what I could do
and then I would say have you thought
about this and said oh yeah that's a
great option as well. So I still had a
lot of conversations and if it's really
solid
>> in the prompt that you gave it, it will
do it perfectly.
>> But giving it more freedom was still
having issues and I was fable. It was
like I had a second team lead.
>> Yeah. What same feeling like
>> and even when he said and I he gave me
options and I was like one is okay, two
is better. Three, what is three? Explain
it to me. And he gave me like a whole
new solution to do it even better.
That's exactly the same like it it feel
for me it feel like a proper co-founder
like technical co-founder where like
that level like that level of like
direction and solution and stuff. So the
future is bright bro.
>> Oh yeah. Imagine it getting even better.
>> Yeah. Like
>> it it starts to talk back to me and say,
"Hey, you're doing it wrong." [laughter]
>> Uh
I saw your tweet. Uh I'm gonna show you
uh when he asked um Fable to uh rate his
codebase and he got toasted. [laughter]
>> But before this was like really good.
You would hire these guys at really high
rates just to get them to do it for you.
And now an AI roast them.
>> Exactly. And it was not fine. It okay.
Maybe also he prompted it as a joke and
stuff. But uh that was uh that was uh
>> Yeah, but if it can't find anything
wrong then there is nothing wrong.
>> Yeah. I mean yeah until you ask uh are
you sure and then it go oh yeah by the
way I found that and that and that.
>> Yeah. Um where is it? Uh
>> well the cool thing is with Fable if it
came back with the new solutions and I
asked one okay what sort of companies
use it? He said, "Yeah, like enterprise
level." So I said, "Well, that takes a
long time to set up. Maybe we do this
first." And he said, "Oh, no, no, no.
It's like a few setups and it doesn't
even take more time than the way that
you do it." And I just set it up
properly.
>> Yeah. No, no, like the estimation of uh
task and implementation is garbage
because again, it was trained on human
implementation time.
>> But AI is, "Oh yeah, no, we need three
weeks to implement that, bro. You can do
it in five minutes. Shut the [__] up."
>> Yeah. Yeah. And even if you ask, it's
normally 3 weeks. How long does it take
when I use like two AI agents who do it
for me? He still says a week. [laughter]
>> Mental. But okay. So you uh Okay. Uh I'm
going to
>> do you know what the issue is then?
Maybe AI still thinks that we read
everything.
>> Oh,
>> just wait for the moment that it knows
that we don't read the code it creates.
Then we have a problem. I'm I'm already
here, bro. Because uh
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
That's gonna That's gonna be a good
point. Okay. Uh okay. We don't care
about this this tweet anymore.
>> Yeah.
>> So, reviewing code
>> Mhm. If [clears throat]
the cost of writing code is zero
and you can ship fast, what's the point
of reviewing
code that you can instantly fix anyway?
>> The only thing is there is a difference
in reviewing between having a bug and
not working and having it working but
being insecure.
Yes, but uh at some point the models
will also
be able to write better code that any
fun engineers.
>> Yeah. So they don't you don't write it.
You just test it if it is user friendly
>> that that yes like the taste of codeex
5.5 or even like uh 4.8. I didn't do any
front end with fable. I mean did I maybe
maybe a bit but uh I still use Opus 4.8
for front. Um but yes what I do is like
I run the app on local and even on
production like with the
extension and then code is uh click
click click on the app and then I can
say okay this one is broken and then uh
change that then you still have to
describe that you want but uh it's
getting better [clears throat] and
better and yes soon enough it should
like memorize what you want or even like
have the guidelines of all of the
project and keep following the
guidelines and the MD file that you
have. So then it's done like it knows
that I don't want it to not use my
shared component like a card or a table.
I don't want him to create a HTML table.
I I want it to use my table component.
So then it will always looks the same,
you know.
>> Yeah, that's perfect.
So yeah, it just like you have a wide
engineers that need guard rails and your
job is just like giving like put him on
the rails. But yeah, it can execute like
crazy stuff. Like for example, I never
coded with Swift. I always did like um
um
hybrid apps.
>> Mhm. But no, I have two or three apps
that I use on my Mac like the Mac sweep
clean and the metabar stuff completely
sweep swift native code.
Never read a line of code. Okay, it's a
small tool stuff, right?
>> But it works. I have a nice user
experience with it and that's it
>> and it's perfect and you use it for
yourself. So it's not to scale and
>> Yes. I mean yeah and and it doesn't
needs to scale like crazy in term of
okay uh it's going to touch your
computer it's open source so people can
review the code whatever whatever um so
it's fine yes okay I'm not building
Twitch so fair enough
>> I think that's still also a big
difference some of the tools that I make
that are running locally
>> or even in a GitHub and we just pull
them to everybody in a company but
everybody runs it locally not on the
internet Then yeah, just let it run. I
don't even check. It just needs to work.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. And I could see
like even a a future where like you use
more apps than web cloud based stuff
because at scale like you could even
maybe you have like yeah server
synchronization and stuff like that but
you
um relocate the server effort to your
user computers.
>> Yes,
>> there is some Yeah. stuff like that. But
yeah, I don't know. I don't know how
that will change. But yeah, Feb Feb 5
was great. I know it's coming.
>> You know it's coming. So what's coming
next?
>> Uh 5.6 like soon, please.
>> And they promise us it was better.
>> Yeah. I mean, okay. So Chibo
Chiu, do do you know this guy? Not this
guy. This guy. This guy.
He's a guy who has the power to reset
our Codex subscription
and um Ultra will be in Codex with 1
million views for reply.
>> Yeah,
>> open OpenAI missed a tricky uh a trick
by keeping 5.5 Pro out of Codex. With
Codex having much higher usage limit and
open eye giving out so many reset,
there's basically no reason to pay for
clone max 20 uh right now. No, I really
hope they had 5.6 Pro or so ultra to
Codex. Ultra will be on Codex.
>> Yeah. And he even has like so much more
views than the person with the original.
>> Yeah, because everyone is like quoting.
But uh yeah, it's it's going to be nuts.
Um closing. Okay, I don't care about
that. Uh, okay. It was working. Yes. Uh,
and they are teasing it like hard. So, I
think it's coming soon. Uh,
>> even if you just think about the
marketing, they know that people want it
because they use Fable.
>> Yeah.
>> And now Fable is being taken away and
put behind a very expensive API.
>> Exactly. So I would wait and I would
just say eventually well to everybody
come to us we have it for you and it is
cheaper and better
>> and and you don't have credits because
uh you can press the reset button
whatever you want.
>> Yeah.
>> And entropy can catch up because they
don't have the little computers to run
like see uh GPT 5.6 solar ultra uh 92%
5.6 six soul which is like the yeah it's
the big uh fable five mitos uh uh GPT
right equivalent right but it's at the
same level slightly above it
>> yeah they had one question more in the
correct way so they
>> oh
>> for the 0.8% 8%.
>> Yeah, could be. Yeah. Uh, okay. Yeah.
So, even like the Terra, which which
will be like the I think the first one.
No, it's Moon, Terra, and Soul, right?
So, it will be probably like the
equivalent of like XI or high and it's
at the same level of Fable 5. So, wait,
what? 5.5 is at the No, that's not true.
>> No, that's not true.
>> Okay, maybe uh maybe this short is
[__]
Search for the real benchmark they gave
us.
>> Yeah, but I don't think we have it,
right?
Uh 5.6 model available only to selected
trust partner. So that's cool. Uh 5.5
low is fast. Imagine 5 sold on Sarah
Brass. Okay, whatever. Oh yeah. See,
Cerras, that was the what the the
company that uh Nick uh was talking
about.
>> Mhm.
>> Last week.
Uh
uh so 5 bit. So 5.6 soul ultra already
bit five a fable five on terminal bench.
Okay. So that's what we saw. Um I'm
going to try to find the charge again.
Half the price less guardrail killing
normal coding task. No weekly limit that
sales build up running 24 hours.
>> Yeah.
>> So you just buy another subscription
after 24 hours.
>> Yeah. That that's going to get shipped.
That going to get expensive if we do
that again. Um
uh wait what upcoming prediction? Yeah.
Okay.
Okay. I lost the tweet. Oh okay. So no
that looks like the chart is legit.
uh 5.6 launches next week which is uh
yeah the same week entropic pull pulls
Fable 5 from subscription
uh tech t tech yeah okay so the
benchmark I don't understand the 5.5 in
fable 5 in my wasn't the gap that small
>> I don't think so I didn't use codeex 5.5
with I was full cloud last week but
Yeah. Okay. So maybe
>> if the better one is coming just uh I
don't care. Give me the better one.
>> Oh yes. Exactly. Uh so Saul it will be
the big big one. Terra and Luna. So Luna
will be the equivalent of Sunny maybe
and Terra Opus and Soul will be Fable
I guess.
>> Mhm. [clears throat]
>> I mean they already have it but yeah
whatever. Uh 5.56.
What do you guys think will be a lot of
error? I mean, even if it's at the same
level, but with the codeex usage, that's
it. It's game over.
Like, how long? Oh, no. Entropic has uh
the deal with uh
>> Yeah. with Right.
>> Yeah. Do we know like how long they need
to start the servers?
>> I don't know.
>> Yeah. Because
>> the only thing I know is that even now
with using Fable
>> in the nightly hours, so when it was US
time,
>> it would be slower than in my mornings
and it would even sometimes just give
issues.
>> Oh yeah, like the server API like uh
>> not not available. Yeah, that's
annoying. Uh it's
there was entropic compute
uh yeah okay
can I can find it but yeah okay and then
uh if it's not chat GPT uh GPT 5.6 uh
are you going to start to call some
Chinese models?
>> No, I'm just using the 5.5 and the Opus.
>> Yeah. And only if one of my customers
really wants Fable, he has to pay for
it. But I'm not spending that much money
on the model. But Fable made so much. I
I made him uh create a road map for the
coming six months
>> on every project
>> and that's like a full day of of coding
instead of six months because it says,
"Oh, we can do this in this month, but
still you can do it in an hour."
>> Yeah. Uh, so I have a lot of work left.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So like like last time like
you max out fable to plan everything
out, right?
>> Yeah. And then just the next two or
three weeks you can keep on going with
Opus and Codeex.
>> Yeah. Exactly. And by that time
hopefully you have 5.6
>> the next one.
>> Yeah. Uh did you try like the GPTs at
all like the
the initial uh launch you know like the
open source from
uh OpenAI introduction GP2s was that
>> no I didn't test it
>> that was oh what okay oh that was last
year yes
so yeah
I mean
>> if you need to test everything it is
just too much.
>> Yeah. And yeah, again like when you have
a code and codexc subscription like you
don't need that. But uh what can you do
on a models that have been posted
in October last year compared to now?
That's tricky too, right?
Because also we're building like
workflow for the models that are live
and frontier right now. I don't want to
come back six months too late even if
it's free.
>> No, but you're also building it now when
you're creating prompts and you see the
results and you approve it and if you
get a model that's not as good, the
results will be very bad.
>> Yeah. True. Yeah.
>> Because it cannot handle the setup that
you have created.
>> Yeah. Like the organization and like the
Yeah. like the sub agent potential blah
blah blah benchmark
tech
[__] arena
AI bench mark max
because even right now like the
um
cloud fable 5 yes um the the the private
labs are winning anyway like all of the
models. Okay. The top 10 models are like
all entropic or
uh open eye.
>> Yeah. But when you have a good model,
you just use it to train.
>> So if you have an edge and you are the
front runner, you use that one to train
your next one. Then people need to work
really hard to get
>> Yeah.
>> Or they can distill your models. That's
a problem, too.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. If if you if you come out with a
so with AI now that you have uh the
training that cost you1 billion dollar
and then other people are uh distilling
it for 100k and now they have a1 billion
uh dollarsish
um even if you get 50% it's still a big
improvement
>> but I think that's why uh cloud block
China right
>> or they put And they were talking about
putting in the spyware to see who in
China was stealing the data and blocking
everything
>> really
I mean can they really
>> I don't know it was on X so try search
it
>> China bans entropic AI from employation
what the okay fair enough
claps back at entropic yeah I mean if
you lose China. That's a big market. So
that's annoying.
>> Yeah. Well, Trump blocked it anyway. So
>> yeah. [laughter]
Yeah. That's that, bro. That's a massive
discussion because again in Europe like
okay, we have like 300. So it's another
like US market is with less buying power
than the US. But it's like 400 million
um market 400 million people market.
Can they ban uh Europe of usage of any
AI?
>> Yeah. Well, even if you say they cannot,
they do it with everything.
>> Yeah. And it makes sense with
intelligence, right? Because you say,
"Oh, sorry, Rob. Uh you can't use OpenAI
or Entropic and we're going to keep
doing intelligence for us. See you in
six months."
>> Uh that's it. Like Yeah.
>> There's no more economy in Europe at
all. No. Can you imagine that?
>> At least the smart people are then
moving out.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Are you moving to the US?
>> Yeah. Yeah. [laughter]
I am at that moment.
>> Yeah, bro. Like I'm I'm Canadian too. I
have the passport. So, let's go.
>> Perfect.
>> You AI immigr uh no not immigr uh alien.
We are AI alien. Hi. What's up?
Um
>> but that's a question right for the uh
codex 5.6
if cloud was blocked how is codex going
to get approved directly and not being
blocked for the public outside the US
>> because they worked with uh the white
house before launching it. That's why it
was in preview and now we will get it
but all of the big cops got it like one
or two weeks ago. So better
preparations.
>> Yeah, I know. Exactly. Better
preparation and probably like kiss more
houses than entropic. But it could be
that too because they have the like
entropic is a bit of like also like
against the administration blah blah
blah and the administration is bit like
susceptible.
So if you don't kiss the house, they're
not going to like you. And looks like
OpenAI was a bit better at that. So,
Antropic was bit uh push away and open
AAI is closer uh to the white house. So,
then that gave like premium access I
guess
>> to
>> Yeah, I mean yeah don't just don't block
her please. But other than that,
>> let let us cook. Let us cook.
>> Um okay. Yeah, just quickly back to the
benchmark stuff. Um
>> uh what? Oh, did I lost it? I lost it.
Thank
um
so
we have No, I I can't even do labs. Yes,
Labs. Entropic OpenAI then it's like a
Z.AI with GLM 5.2 but net improvement.
Yeah, with their highest models. So,
confirmation of success 1669.
Okay. So, that's on the benchmark,
right? But uh so the labs is third and
the model is Yeah. Okay. It's a top 10.
Okay. Now, GLM 5.2. It's a big uh it's a
big step for the open source.
>> Yeah. But it takes so much compute.
then you can use um the subscription on
uh Z.AI.
So they put their model open source, but
you can also pay for uh the sub.
>> Do they have the I never looked at it.
Do they have the prices?
>> Yeah, it's cheaper than um than uh
>> it's a Yeah, they all look the same, but
>> Yeah. Yeah, because why not? Uh Z ai
slash
pricing.
Let's go. Okay. Value subscription.
Okay. Oh, okay. Let's go.
>> Uh I don't want chat.
I want coding plan. Yes. Subscribe now.
Light Pro Max 100 a month.
Uh, and yeah, and you get uh 20x. So,
exactly the same pricing model.
>> It looks like a full ripoff.
>> Oh, yeah. I know. I mean, yeah. Welcome
to China, man. But, uh, it's it's
cheaper, right? So if you are a bit on a
budget and you get that kind of
intelligence
then
>> yeah but still before if you hired a
deaf for like two hours you would have
the same cost as now a full month of a
pro license.
>> So for just those few dollars
>> then I would go with the best one.
>> Yeah. No, of course.
>> If I'm fully thinking about privacy,
want to have a local, not paying at all,
then I'm I'm using a big machine, but
otherwise just give me Cloud Fable.
>> Yes, but you you can't even install 5.2
on like a big machine right now. Like
you need Yeah.
>> Like you need a proper server and you
need half a million dollar to run that
[__]
>> Yeah. And like five cooling fans to keep
everything on temperature.
>> Exactly. Like yeah uh if you want those
if you want those model at home uh
you're going to buy back your
subscription with electricity.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. For sure.
>> Like so yeah like the alternative. Okay.
The alternative doesn't exist. Bye. See
you end of the video. [laughter]
>> But okay. So on on this arena benchmark
stuff 5 5.2 max is at the level of 5.4I.
for I which is also massive
>> but they have the distillation period
basically so frontier model launch a
model private get distill
um z.ai AI or any other like what was
the other one? Deepseek. Deepseek is
distilling those models. Get the their
open source model back sell
subscription. Boom.
>> Yes. True.
>> So yeah,
I mean like we legit have one generation
away. So basically 3 to 6 months
um lag between frontier and open source
models. So that means in like 12 to 18
months we will have open source model
who have fable five intelligence.
>> Yeah that's insane. But by that time I
hope to have built so much.
>> Yeah
>> it doesn't.
>> But what are you going to build
>> everything?
No, but before you had to plan because
building a a proper software tool would
take you at least a year to do it
properly,
>> sales and everything. And now you just
choose a niche, you build it within two,
three days, and you start selling.
>> Yeah. Uh yeah, I tried that. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Well, you're making like a huge
system with every functionality in it.
>> Yeah. I I I think Okay. So, yeah, I
think you're right. like with those
model now we can even see a big wave of
uh oneshot software.
>> Yeah.
>> Because Yeah. Even like the
the game like so the the game with one
one shot prompted. Okay. That's that's a
little bit buggy, but you spend like uh
one or two days on it, then you have
proper something like proper like
something with what which is fun
>> and then you can market these uh games
to like we're going to have a lot of
stream uh steam games slope especially
when Unreal Engine is making it like MCP
and then everyone can access. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Talk to it and it will build
it.
>> Yeah. Exactly. But we're getting there
like for sure. And yeah, like for those
fable five level models. Yeah, bro. We
have 12 months to cook like starting
now.
>> Yeah. So, what are we going to build?
>> Let's go. Let's go. Uh I um I So, based
on fable feedback,
>> Mhm. I asked um
uh GPT5 to where should we take this
road map direction blah blah blah and I
could build a SAS for uh generating
assets like kind of like Genfit but with
like the vertical of uh gaming.
>> Mhm.
>> Where you have your own uh studio inside
of the
um
Yeah. I mean that's it. But uh yeah and
then open source and whatever there is a
couple of open source solution but uh
probably can do something better I don't
know so there is that still genfit and
still like customers project that where
we can
either do mega apps of one verticals
that do everything or small uh small
tiny s micro sasses but then you make
like 10 20 of them and
hopefully some of them catch up to 5 10k
20k months m
>> well that's good enough and if you have
like five to 10 of those that's
perfectly
>> exactly and there's a lot of like indie
actors who are basically doing that but
uh you can serve them like the the the
world is your oyster right so you can uh
>> keep building some stuff that works and
uh yeah just try it and if it doesn't
work you trash it you go to the next
one.
>> Yeah, you just improve it or delete it.
>> Yeah, like uh trustm.com.
Like I show you this uh this software,
right? Uh
so it's a uh it's a platform where you
connect your stripe key
>> in read only and you can see the revenue
of those platform.
So
um you so then those platform can uh
like the founder can flex oh yeah I
build I v coded this app and then this
is my revenue trust me because I'm on
trust emer
>> and but what's smart too is now that you
can buy SAS that are generating revenue
like if you want to uh buy an AI
visibility SAS with a paid growth
dashboard for businesses that want to be
recommended by chat GPT code. Okay, so
it's a GEO uh business
making revenue blah blah blah boom and
uh you can see the whole revenue based
on stripe stuff and uh contact the guy
and try to buy the
>> Yeah, buy the SAS and so you have some
they prove that it is making money.
>> Exactly. But what's tricky if if I see
that how hard can I replicate the
product in a week and start sales week
two?
>> Yeah. Yeah. But eventually it's not
about building. It's about doing proper
sales.
>> Exactly. But if you are if you are an
influencer with like some distribution
channels then
>> this is awesome
>> coding that that's awesome. Yeah.
So yeah. And okay, so this guy from uh
tech from this platform, where is he?
Yeah, Mark. Bam. Perfect. Puff.
Uh so he has all of his business on his
own landing page.
>> Cut fast 9K. Ship fast 3K a month. Data
fast 20K. Trust 37K a month for the
platform. [snorts]
Focus on your startup knowing the
invoice 100 amounts pop up. Okay. So you
get some SS not going nowhere but
okay.
>> Yeah it still is build a lot and only
focus on the views that take off.
>> Yeah but like trust in one month you pay
for all of your looks like memecoin bro.
Yeah,
>> like you buy one income, you you win one
and then you you pay back for 1,000 uh
um 1,000 fail uh and scam that you have
invested. But yeah, okay. So look, he's
making like 100k months.
>> I think his biggest product is this
website because he is getting so many
DMs from pretty women who want someone
who has money. Exactly. [laughter]
Build your indie page. Oh, okay.
Indie page nice. Okay, that's pretty
cool. Yeah, see like those kind of like
that's that's perfect. One pass 25 years
lifetime deal. Yeah. So, basically it's
a link link tree page but for all of the
indie a boom
um and it has like a YouTube channel
with like 200
thousand subscribers. So
>> yeah,
>> distribution as soon as you have
distribution, you can do all of those
small project
>> and it doesn't even matter what you
build.
>> Exactly. Exactly. So yeah, that's the
alternative to Febru 5. Great content.
Uh yeah, I I I like I like this mindset
of like and AI is perfect for that. I I
like it. So cool.
Uh okay, what else? What else do we
have?
Well, um,
>> we need a countdown. When is U We don't
know what what is the countdown until um
Fable goes offline.
>> Uh, I I thought
>> it was supposed to be like 10 hours ago.
>> Ah, yeah. I couldn't try anymore because
I'm maxed out until Friday.
>> Me, too.
>> I'm not going to buy another $200 sub
for just two or three hours left.
>> Yeah, I know. Exactly. Uh but also yeah
look there is a rumor here Feb 5 access
could be part of the code pro 20x
subscription
>> according to connected to to totropic or
is he just
>> no I think he's quoting another tweet is
okay see that was like the same account
that I've read the charts
um February running locally in about two
years okay so that's different um
but Yeah, that's I could see it
happening though like because how many
200 the month subscription do they have?
But the problem is like okay so you pay
200 but you spend 5k of uh tokens anyway
so the math is not muffing.
>> No no because all the people using the
20x sub are the ones spending a lot of
money.
>> Exactly. So yeah. Okay. Okay. Yeah. No,
you're right. Maybe it will not happen.
>> Can give me one moment.
>> Yeah.
Okay.
Hi.
>> Hello.
>> Uh, okay.
>> What are we doing? What are we waiting
for? What are we going to do?
I
>> I'm like right now I'm kind of like
waiting for 5.6 to drop now. Like
>> yeah. So we are just refreshing the
timeline all the time waiting for the
moment that they push the
>> Yeah. Because Okay. So if you use um
5.5 now
>> Mhm.
>> like [clears throat] how much slop are
you going to push?
>> Um but it doesn't matter. You can either
prompt uh write prompts or you can now
just build with five 5.5 put it in a
different branch and as soon as 5.6 tick
comes out, you say, "Hey, this was my
branch.
>> Check everything." And it will optimize
your code.
>> So, you push as much PR that you can and
then uh you will review everything.
Yeah. Makes sense.
>> Yeah. Then you don't have to explain
what you want to do.
>> Yeah. So, basically, you prepare for the
next uh upcoming models. Uh hopefully
we're not going to have uh to wait too
much too too many things and that's kind
of
>> because I have like over 100 branches
with code waiting to be reviewed.
But you know that's um what the like
same thing again like the another video
of his like he was on the convers
conference and he was uh coding on his
um uh on his T3 code mobile app and
Fable shipped what he thought will take
a month to review and ship and it didn't
have to review as much it was reviewing
before like
uh
>> yeah but before we were building with by
5.5 as well so it
>> won't be that big of an issue
>> but uh you you don't know okay I don't
know what I ship until it's broken
[laughter]
>> t
um [snorts] you should be re reviewing
as much a much smaller percent of your
code today than you were five years ago
if your code is important It need every
line verified. You better writing a lot
of slope that verify these two. Yeah.
Before AI writen review merge. Okay.
After ai writon generated review merge.
[snorts]
>> Well, it just create a street.
It's like or of a big loop with
everything in it. [clears throat]
>> And then you don't need to do a proper
testing. It just have have it switch uh
to different agents and do testing for
you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And like jungling between
again like the smaller models
for task front job whatever whatever we
have and the big brain for planning.
Yeah. I I think that's a clear after
this week that's a clear future where we
can see software engineer for sure.
>> Yes.
>> Uh should we wrap it up here?
>> Yeah.
I think I will have a video.
>> We will give a update on the channel
once 5.6 is out.
>> Yeah, that I think we have
we have our stream for next week. That's
for sure.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But we also have a X
account, right?
So if you follow it, we will let you
know when 5.6 is out.
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Smart. Just
smart. [laughter]
>> In case you don't follow Antropic
yourself. Yeah.
>> Or or Open AI.
>> Yeah. Follow us instead. Yeah. No news
from entropic account.
>> Nothing.
>> That's all spam. Don't follow them.
>> Yeah. No, exactly. We don't need that.
We don't want that. Open AI. Open AI.
Nothing dropped during No. Nothing
dropped. We're safe.
>> Yes.
>> So, yeah. Um, okay. Con conclusion. Did
we have a conclusion? Did we conclude?
>> Yeah. We had a great week and probably
we got an even better week upcoming.
>> Nice. That will end the video. Let's go.
Rachel, thank you so much for your time
and
>> let's get back to prompting some plans
that we will review by Smarter Models.
[laughter]
>> Awesome. Thank you. Enjoy your day.